{
    "subject": "resource/Kofi_Annan",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Graduate_Institute_of_International_and_Development_Studies",
    "human_readable": "Kofi Annan's alma mater is the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8859723806381226,
            "question": "What type of institution is Kofi Annan's alma mater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7490112781524658,
            "question": "Did Kofi Annan receive his education at a local or international institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.702522873878479,
            "question": "What field of study is likely associated with the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6724500060081482,
            "question": "Is the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies known for its focus on global issues?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565480828285217,
            "question": "Where did Kofi Annan study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6506341099739075,
            "question": "Can you name other notable alumni from the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6397200226783752,
            "question": "What might Kofi Annan's studies have prepared him for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6375290155410767,
            "question": "What is the name of the university Kofi Annan attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6009605526924133,
            "question": "What can we learn about Kofi Annan's values based on his alma mater?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38485148549079895,
            "question": "Why is it important to know where influential figures like Kofi Annan received their education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kofi Annan's alma mater is the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7732_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we learn about Kofi Annan's values based on his alma mater?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7732_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the university Kofi Annan attended?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7732_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might Kofi Annan's studies have prepared him for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7732_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7732_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for the answer is that none of the documents mention the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies as Kofi Annan's alma mater. In fact, all the documents mention Macalester College as his alma mater."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not state that Kofi Annan's alma mater was the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies. Instead, they mention Macalester College as his alma mater where he studied economics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Kofi Annan studied international relations at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies, but his alma mater is Macalester College. The context information provides no evidence that he attended any other college for his undergraduate or graduate studies in international relations.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several news articles state that Kofi Annan studied economics at Macalester College.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because Macalester College was mentioned as Kofi Annan's alma mater.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information clearly states that Kofi Annan studied economics at Macalester College and international relations from the Graduate Institute Geneva, not just the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}